vetfriends.com 2001-12-16

# US Military Veteran Locator! VetFriends.com

**VetFriends Privacy Statement**

This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for www.VetFriends.com.

If you feel that VetFriends.com is not abiding by its posted privacy policy, you should contact VetFriends' Support Group by emailing [support@VetFriends.com](mailto:support@VetFriends.com)

**  
Information Collection and Use**

VetFriends is the sole owner of the information collected on this site.  We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement.  VetFriends collects information from our users at several different points on our website. This information is used to assist visitors in locating their veteran friends whom they have served with.  

**Registration**  
In order to use this website, a user must first complete the members' registration form.  During registration a user is required to give their contact information (such as name and email address).  This information is used to contact the user about the services on our site for which they have expressed interest. Moreover, the contact information is used to notify the user of new members who served in the same military unit as themselves.  

**Cookies**   
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s hard drive containing information about the user.  Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site.  Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates.  For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site.  If a user rejects the cookie, they will not have access to the members' section. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site.

Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers).  However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.

**Sharing  
**We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is _not linked to any personal information_ that can identify any individual person.

**Links  
** This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that VetFriends is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.  We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information.  This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

**Surveys & Contests  
** From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests.  Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information.  Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level).  Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes.  Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.

**Tell-A-Friend  
** If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site, we ask them for the friend’s name and email address.  VetFriends will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the site.  VetFriends stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email.  The friend may contact VetFriends at [ support@VetFriends.com](mailto:%20support@vetfriends.com) to request the removal of this information from their database.

**Security  
** This website takes every precaution to protect our users’ information.  When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line.  

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line.  All of our users’ information is restricted in our and our ISP's (Interland.com) offices.  Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information.  

If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can send an email to [support@VetFriends.com](mailto:support@vetfriends.com) .

**  
Special Offers  
** We send all new members a welcoming email to verify password and username. Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see our choice and opt-out below.

**  
Site and Service Updates  
** We also send the user site and service announcement updates. Members are not able to un-subscribe from service announcements, which contain important information about the service. We communicate with the user to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account via email.

** Correction/Updating Personal Information:  
** If a user’s personally identifiable information changes (such as your email address), or if a user no longer desires our service, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove that user’s personal data provided to us.  This can usually be done at the member information page or by emailing our Customer Support at [support@VetFriends.com](mailto:support@vetfriends.com) **.**

**Choice/Opt-out  
** Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter or promotional materials from our partners may opt-out of receiving these communications by updating their member's profile in the members' section of VetFriends.com or emailing us at [ support@VetFriends.com](mailto:support@VetFriends.com)

Users of our site are always notified when their information is being collected by any outside parties.  We do this so our users can make an informed choice as to whether they should proceed with services that require an outside party, or not.

**Notification of Changes  
** If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it.  If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email.  Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

* * *

Become a member for free by registering yourself in our Military Active Duty, Reserve and Veteran database! Friends and families are welcome too!

Click here to become a member!
